Guide to the Dick Thornburgh Papers, 1932- AIS.1998.30.13
ULS Archives & Special Collections
- Attorney General of the United States, 1988-1991; XIII.
  - Events, 7.
    - Press Events
      - "Justice" Publication Inaugural Symposium, Washington, DC, September 17, 1990 (Box 816, Folder 34)
      - Justice Symposium, Voting Rights, Washington, DC, November 16, 1990 (Box 816, Folder 35)
      - Justice Symposium, Environmental Law, Washington, DC, June 27, 1991 (Box 816, Folder 36)
      - Kansas City Crime Commission, "Crackdown" on Crime, Kansas City, MO, October 25, 1990 (Box 816, Folder 37)
      - KDKA Radio (Pittsburgh, PA), Washington, DC, October 26, 1990 (Box 816, Folder 38)
      - KDKA Radio (Pittsburgh, PA), Paul Martino interview, Washington, DC, December 5, 1989 (Box 816, Folder 39)
      - KDKA Radio (Pittsburgh, PA) Ray Tannehill interview on Three Mile Island (TMI), Washington, DC, February 17, 1989 (Box 816, Folder 40)
      - Khun Sa Indictment (Heroin), Washington, DC, March 15, 1990 (Box 816, Folder 41)
      - Kilpatrick, Jack, Washington, DC, December 22, 1988 (Box 817, Folder 1)
      - Kiplinger letter, Charles Snyder and Gene Goldenberg, Washington, DC, February 16, 1989 (Box 817, Folder 2)
      - Knight-Ridder, News Bureau, Washington, DC, February 10, 1989 (Box 817, Folder 3)
      - Knight-Ridder, Aaron Epstein interview, Washington, DC, February 7, 1989 (Box 817, Folder 4)
      - Knight-Ridder, Sandy Grady interview, Washington, DC, September 28, 1990 (Box 817, Folder 5)
      - LaFrankie, Suzanne, WPVI-TV 6 (Philadelphia, PA) interview, Harrisburg, PA, January 17, 1989 (Box 817, Folder 6)
      - Law Enforcement Television Network (Dallas, TX), Carrollton, TX, October 8, 1990, October 31, 1990 (Box 817, Folder 7)
      - Law Enforcement Television Network, Forum Interview, Washington, DC, February 7, 1991 (Box 817, Folder 8)
      - Los Angeles Daily Journal, Washington, DC, July 17, 1989 (Box 817, Folder 9)
      - Los Angeles Times, Washington Bureau, Washington, DC, February 15, 1989 (Box 817, Folder 10)
      - Los Angeles Times, Editorial Board, Los Angeles, CA, April 24, 1989 (Box 817, Folder 11)
      - Los Angeles Times, Ron Ostrow interview regarding Soviet Union trip (and others), Washington, DC, March 24, 1989, May 17, 1989, October 11, 1989, October 12, 1989, March 15, 1990, May 22, 1990 (Box 817, Folder 12)
      - Media General, Steve Goldberg interview, Washington, DC, May 24, 1990 (Box 817, Folder 13)
      - Mexican Television, Washington, DC, September 26, 1989 (Box 817, Folder 14)
      - Miller, Arthur, WCVB-TV, Boston interview, Washington, DC, January 18, 1989 (Box 817, Folder 15)
      - Milwaukee Journal, Editorial Board, Milwaukee, WI, August 17, 1989 (Box 817, Folder 16)
      - Milwaukee Sentinel, Editorial Board, Milwaukee, WI, August 17, 1989 (Box 817, Folder 17)
      - "Modern Maturity" television program, Washington, DC, August 23, 1988 (Box 817, Folder 18)
      - Moll, Richard, interview, Washington, DC, March 23, 1989 (Box 817, Folder 19)
      - Money Laundering/Jose Gacha Press Conference, Washington, DC, December 6, 1989 (Box 817, Folder 20)
      - Moody Indictment Announcement with Sessions, Washington, DC, November 7, 1990 (Box 817, Folder 21)
      - McBirney/Sunbelt Savings and Loan Indictment Announcement, Washington, DC, July 11, 1990 (Box 817, Folder 22)
      - McLaughlin, John, "One on One" Show, Washington, DC, June 23, 1989, August 2, 1990 (Box 817, Folder 23)
      - "MacNeil/Lehrer Newshour," Washington, DC, October 4, 1990, March 11, 1991 (Box 817, Folder 24)
      - "MacNeil/Lehrer Newshour," Anniversary Dinner, Washington, DC, October 9, 1990 (Box 817, Folder 25)
      - "MacNeil/Lehrer Newshour," Crime Bill, Arlington, VA, June 13, 1991 (Box 817, Folder 26)
      - "MacNeil/Lehrer Newshour," Judy Woodruff interview, Arlington, VA, August 28, 1989 (Box 817, Folder 27)
      - NBC Mutual Radio, Bonnie Erbe interview, Washington, DC, August 16, 1990 (Box 817, Folder 28)
      - NBC News, Lisa Meyers interview, Washington, DC, April 20, 1990 (Box 817, Folder 29)
      - NBC News, Andrea Mitchell interview, Washington, DC, April 12, 1990 (Box 817, Folder 30)
      - NBC News "Meet the Press," Washington, DC, January 22, 1989, August 20, 1989 (Box 817, Folder 31)
      - NBC News "Meet the Press," Washington, DC, June 30, 1991 (Box 817, Folder 32)
      - NBC Nightly News, Garrick Utley interview, Washington, DC, May 5, 1991 (Box 817, Folder 33)
      - NBC "Today Show," Bryant Gumbel interview, Washington, DC, October 3, 1989 (Box 817, Folder 34)
      - NBC "Today Show," Katherine (Katie) Couric interview, Washington, DC, July 12, 1990 (Box 817, Folder 35)
      - National Drug Control Strategy II, Satellite Interviews, Washington, DC, January 25, 1990 (Box 817, Folder 36)
      - National Journal, John Moore interview, Washington, DC, January 24, 1989 (Box 817, Folder 37)
      - National Journal, Jonathan Rauch interview, Washington, DC, May 3, 1989 (Box 817, Folder 38)
      - National Newspaper Association, Washington, DC, March 15, 1991 (Box 817, Folder 39)
      - National Press Club Luncheon, Three Mile Island (TMI), Washington, DC, March 28, 1989 (Box 817, Folder 40)
      - National Press Club Luncheon, Savings & Loan, Washington, DC, July 25, 1990 (Box 817, Folder 41)
      - National Public Radio, Cokie Roberts interview regarding Three Mile Island (TMI), Washington, DC, March 3, 1989 (Box 817, Folder 42)
      - National Public Radio, Nina Totenberg interview, Washington, DC, November 3, 1989 (Box 817, Folder 43)
      - National Public Radio, Claudio Sanchez interview regarding Americans with Disabilities Act (ADA) regulations, Washington, DC, July 22, 1991 (Box 817, Folder 44)
      - National Public Radio, Questions and Answers with Schorr & Totenberg, Washington, DC, February 6, 1990 (Box 817, Folder 45)
      - Nationwide Report on Drug Trafficking press conference, Washington, DC, August 3, 1989 (Box 817, Folder 46)
      - The New Republic, Mark Hosenball interview, Washington, DC, March 13, 1990 (Box 817, Folder 47)
      - Newsday, Bob Kessler interview, Washington, DC, December 1, 1989 (Box 818, Folder 1)
      - Newsfed Network, interview regarding drug policy, Washington, DC, September 6, 1989 (Box 818, Folder 2)
      - Newsweek, Bob Cohn interview, Washington, DC, March 8, 1991 (Box 818, Folder 3)
      - Newsweek, Ann McDaniel and Mark Miller interview, Washington, DC, May 17, 1990 (Box 818, Folder 4)
      - Newsweek, Richard Sandza interview, Washington, DC, August 25, 1989 (Box 818, Folder 5)
      - New York Replacement Window Indictment (organized crime), New York, NY, May 30, 1990 (Box 818, Folder 6)
      - New York Times, editorial board, New York, NY, July 13, 1990 (Box 818, Folder 7)
      - New York Times, David Johnston interview, Washington, DC, March 20, 1991 (Box 818, Folder 8)
      - New York Times, Anthony Lewis interview, Washington, DC, October 6, 1988 (Box 818, Folder 9)
      - New York Times, Anthony Lukas interview, Cambridge, MA, November 16, 1988 (Box 818, Folder 10)
      - New York Times, John McKenzie interview, Washington, DC, October 12, 1988 (Box 818, Folder 11)
      - New York Times, Michael Wines interview, Washington, DC, April 18, 1989 (Box 818, Folder 12)
      - New York Times, Washington Bureau, Washington, DC, March 22, 1991 (Box 818, Folder 13)
      - "Off the Record Club" luncheon, Washington, DC, July 11, 1990 (Box 818, Folder 14)
      - Organized Crime Council Report, Washington, DC, January 31, 1991 (Box 818, Folder 15)
      - Operation Polar Cap, Washington, DC, March 29, 1989 (Box 818, Folder 16-17)
      - Operation Southern Star Announcement, Miami, FL, October 24, 1990 (Box 818, Folder 18)
      - Oregonian, Portland, OR, October 17, 1988 (Box 818, Folder 19)
      - Organized Crime Indictment Announcement, Chicago, IL, February 7, 1990 (Box 818, Folder 20)
      - Organized Crime Indictment Announcement, Newark, NJ, December 19, 1990 (Box 818, Folder 21)
      - Patricia Family (LCN) Indictment, Boston, MA, March 26, 1990 (Box 818, Folder 22)
      - Pennsylvania Drug Grant Announcement, Pittsburgh, PA, February 19, 1991 (Box 818, Folder 23)
      - Pennsylvania Lawyer magazine, Don Sarvey interview, Washington, DC, July 27, 1989 (Box 818, Folder 24)
      - Pennsylvania Television Interview, Washington, DC, January 19, 1989 (Box 818, Folder 25)
      - People magazine, Melissa Herman interview regarding Three Mile Island (TMI), Washington, DC, March 3, 1989 (Box 818, Folder 26)
      - Philadelphia Daily News, John Baer interview, Washington, DC, June 22, 1990 (Box 818, Folder 27)
      - Philadelphia Daily News, Reginald Stuart interview, Washington, DC, July 17, 1989 (Box 818, Folder 28)
      - Philadelphia Inquirer, Matt Purdy interview, Washington, DC, September 8, 1989 (Box 818, Folder 29)
      - Pittsburgh Post Gazette, editorial board, Pittsburgh, PA, April 11, 1989 (Box 818, Folder 30)
      - Pittsburgh Post Gazette, Sally Kalson interview, Washington, DC, May 25, 1989 (Box 818, Folder 31)
      - Pittsburgh Post Gazette, Jack Torry interview, Washington, DC, January 16, 1990 (Box 818, Folder 32)
      - Pittsburgh Press, editorial board, Pittsburgh, PA, April 11, 1989 (Box 818, Folder 33)
      - Pittsburgh Press, Mark Warnick interview, Washington, DC, June 20, 1990 (Box 818, Folder 34)
      - Press conference regarding Memorandum of Understanding Signing Ceremony (effort to supplement Nation's drug treatment capacity by making available unused or underused military facilities as treatment sites), Washington, DC, October 28, 1988 (Box 818, Folder 35)
      - Pressler, Senator Larry, taping of show, Washington, DC, October 14, 1988 (Box 818, Folder 36)
      - Project Triggerlock Conference, Orlando, FL, May 6, 1991 (Box 818, Folder 37)
      - Public Corruption Indictment, Chicago, IL, December 19, 1990 (Box 818, Folder 38)
      - Radio America, John Angelus interview, Washington, DC, September 29, 1989 (Box 818, Folder 39)
      - Radio and Television Correspondents' Association Dinner, Washington, DC, March 16, 1989 (Box 818, Folder 40)
      - Raspberry, William, Washington, DC, May 17, 1989 (Box 818, Folder 41)
      - Reichblum, Bob, News director, WJLA-TV, Washington, DC, February 9, 1989 (Box 818, Folder 42)
      - Ripon Forum, Bill McKenzie interview, Washington, DC, August 11, 1989 (Box 818, Folder 43)
      - Safire, William, Washington, DC, June 1, 1990 (Box 818, Folder 44)
      - San Diego Union, editorial board, San Diego, CA, April 21, 1989 (Box 818, Folder 45)
      - Satellite Interviews, Administration accomplishments, Washington, DC, December 21, 1989 (Box 818, Folder 46)
      - Satellite Interviews, Crime Bill, Washington, DC, June 3, 1991 (Box 818, Folder 47)
      - Satellite Interviews, David Souter, Washington, DC, July 24, 1990 (Box 818, Folder 48)
      - Savings and Loan correspondents lunch, Washington, DC, August 7, 1990 (Box 818, Folder 49)
      - Savings and Loan Indictment of Harold Greenwood, former CEO and Chairman of Midwest Federal Savings and Loan, Minneapolis, MN, June 26, 1990 (Box 818, Folder 50)
      - Savings and Loan press conference, Washington, DC, December 7, 1989 (Box 818, Folder 51)
      - Scripps-Howard, John Bennett interview, Washington, DC, February 17, 1989, January 12, 1990 (Box 818, Folder 52)
      - Scripps-Howard, Washington Bureau, Washington, DC, May 23, 1990 (Box 818, Folder 53)
      - Seattle Post-Intelligence, editorial board, Seattle, WA, March 22, 1990 (Box 818, Folder 54)
      - Specter, Senator Arlen, Washington, DC, June 6, 1989 (Box 818, Folder 55)
      - Sperling Group breakfast, Washington, DC, March 7, 1990 (Box 818, Folder 56)
      - State Government News, Linda Wagar interview, Washington, DC, August 15, 1989 (Box 818, Folder 57)
      - States News Service, Washington, DC, November 3, 1989 (Box 818, Folder 58)
      - Tampa Tribune, editorial board, Tampa, FL, November 8, 1990 (Box 818, Folder 59)
      - Teamsters press conference, Washington, DC, March 13, 1989 (Box 819, Folder 1)
      - Thomas, Evan, Chief of Newsweek Washington Bureau, dinner, Washington, DC, February 8, 1989 (Box 819, Folder 2)
      - Thompson Newspapers, Bob Mitchell, Washington, DC, July 6, 1990 (Box 819, Folder 3)
      - Three Mile Island (TMI) Interviews, 10th anniversary, Washington, DC, March 16, 1989, March 24, 1989 (Box 819, Folder 4)
      - TIME, Jerome Kramer interview, Washington, DC, December 7, 1989 (Box 819, Folder 5)
      - TIME, Washington, DC, January 11, 1989 (Box 819, Folder 6)
      - TIME, Washington Bureau, Washington, DC, February 1, 1990 (Box 819, Folder 7)
      - Tulsa Skinheads Indictment Announcement, Tulsa, OK, October 25, 1990 (Box 819, Folder 8)
      - UPI, Russ Snyder, Washington, DC, October 10, 1990 (Box 819, Folder 9)
      - US News and World Report, Steve Hedges interview, Washington, DC, April 7, 1989 (Box 819, Folder 10)
      - US News and World Report, Steve Roberts interview, November 20, 1989 (Box 819, Folder 11)
      - USA Today, editorial board, Arlington, VA, July 24, 1989 (Box 819, Folder 12)
      - USA Today, Richard Benedetto interview, Washington, DC, April 26, 1990 (Box 819, Folder 13)
      - USA Today, Rhonda Graham interview, Washington, DC, July 19, 1990 (Box 819, Folder 14)
      - USA Today, Lee Katz interview, Irvine, CA, June 28, 1990 (Box 819, Folder 15)
      - U.S. Marshals Press Conference on Operation STOP, Washington, DC, July 17, 1989 (Box 819, Folder 16)
      - Victims' Rights, roundtable, Washington, DC, April 22, 1991 (Box 819, Folder 17)
      - Voice of America, Lucy Flam interview, Washington, DC, November 6, 1989 (Box 819, Folder 18)
      - Voice of America Drug Conference, Washington, DC, October 4, 1989 (Box 819, Folder 19)
      - WBZ-TV (Boston, MA), Liz Walker interview, Boston, MA, September 14, 1990 (Box 819, Folder 20)
      - WCAU (Philadelphia, PA) interview on drug policy, Washington, DC, September 5, 1989 (Box 819, Folder 21)
      - WGAL-TV (Lancaster, PA), Keith Martin interview, Washington, DC, January 5, 1989 (Box 819, Folder 22)
      - WTMJ News, Milwaukee, WI, August 17, 1989 (Box 819, Folder 23)
      - Wall Street Journal, Joe Davidson interview, November 13, 1990 (Box 819, Folder 24)
      - Wall Street Journal, Bob Rose interview, Washington, DC, August 2, 1989 (Box 819, Folder 25)
      - Wall Street Journal, Paul Barrett interview, Washington, DC, February 10, 1989 (Box 819, Folder 26)
      - Wall Street Journal, editorial board, New York, NY, October 29, 1990 (Box 819, Folder 27)
      - Washington Bureau Chiefs, Washington, DC, January 23, 1989 (Box 819, Folder 28)
      - Washington Post, editorial board, Washington, DC, May 17, 1990 (Box 819, Folder 29)
      - Washington Post, Sharon LaFraniere interview, Washington, DC, May 30, 1991 (Box 819, Folder 30)
      - Washington Post, Ruth Marcus interview, Washington, DC, December 6, 1989 (Box 819, Folder 31)
      - Washington Post, Spencer Rich interview, article only, undated (Box 819, Folder 32)
      - Washington Press Club, Congressional Dinner, Washington, DC, January 30, 1991 (Box 819, Folder 33)
      - Washington Times, editorial board, Washington, DC, February 14, 1990 (Box 819, Folder 34)
      - "Watch on Washington" with Jack Kilpatrick, Washington, DC, August 9, 1990 (Box 819, Folder 35)
      - "Weed and Seed" press conference, Kansas City, MO, August 7, 1991 (Box 819, Folder 36)
      - "Weed and Seed" press conference, Trenton, NJ, August 7, 1991 (Box 819, Folder 37)
      - "Weed and Seed" press conference, NYU officials, Washington, DC, August 7, 1991 (Box 819, Folder 38)
      - Westin Savings Association Indictment Announcement, Washington, DC, October 25, 1990 (Box 819, Folder 39)
      - Westinghouse Broadcasting Company, Robin Chapman interview, Washington, DC, August 16, 1989 (Box 819, Folder 40)
      - Westinghouse Broadcasting Company, Steve Holt interview, Washington, DC, February 13, 1989 (Box 819, Folder 41)
      - White Collar Crime News Conference, Ed Dennis and Rudy Giuliani, Washington, DC, January 31, 1989 (Box 819, Folder 42)
      - White House Correspondents Association Dinner, Washington, DC, April 28, 1990 (Box 819, Folder 43)
      - Will, George, lunch with Meg Greenfield and Charles Krauthammer, Washington, DC, June 10, 1989 (Box 819, Folder 44)
      - World Monitor Television, Bill O'Connell interview, Washington, DC, September 18, 1990 (Box 819, Folder 45)
      - WorldNet Interview (USIA), Washington, DC, February 2, 1989 (Box 819, Folder 46)
      - WQED Videotaping, Washington, DC, September 22, 1988 (Box 819, Folder 47)
    - Out of Washington, DC Trips
      - Alabama, Montgomery, May 2, 1991 (Box 820, Folder 1)
      - Alabama, Point Clear, November 21, 1988 (Box 820, Folder 2)
      - Alaska, Anchorage, August 31, 1990 (Box 820, Folder 3)
      - Arizona, Phoenix, March 20, 1989 (Box 820, Folder 4)
      - Arizona, Tucson, January 16, 1991 (Box 820, Folder 5)
      - Arizona, Tucson, July 15, 1991 (Box 820, Folder 6)
      - California, Los Angeles, April 20, 1989 (Box 820, Folder 7)
      - California, Los Angeles and San Diego, June 27, 1990 (Box 820, Folder 8)
      - California, Los Angeles, July 10, 1989 (Box 820, Folder 9)
      - California, Los Angeles, February 2, 1991 (Box 820, Folder 10)
      - California, San Diego, April 20, 1989 (Box 820, Folder 11)
      - California, San Francisco, March 23, 1990 (Box 820, Folder 12)
      - Colorado, Denver, June 26, 1990 (Box 820, Folder 13)
      - Colorado, Denver, February 4, 1989 (Box 820, Folder 14)
      - Connecticut, New Haven, June 3, 1989 (Box 820, Folder 15)
      - Connecticut, New Haven, October 6, 1989 (Box 820, Folder 16)
      - Connecticut, Waterbury, August 24, 1989 (Box 820, Folder 17)
      - Delaware, Newark, June 7, 1989 (Box 820, Folder 18)
      - Florida, Miami, April 27, 1989 (Box 820, Folder 19)
      - Florida, Miami, October 24, 1990 (Box 820, Folder 20)
      - Florida, Miami, December 13, 1990 (Box 820, Folder 21)
      - Florida, Orlando, May 6, 1991 (Box 820, Folder 22)
      - Florida, Tallahassee, October 24, 1990 (Box 820, Folder 23)
      - Florida, Tampa, November 14, 1989 (Box 820, Folder 24)
      - Florida, Tampa, November 8, 1990 (Box 820, Folder 25)
      - Florida, Tampa, May 30, 1991 (Box 820, Folder 26)
      - Florida, West Palm Beach, February 20, 1989 (Box 821, Folder 1)
      - Georgia, Atlanta (Martin Luther King Day), January 16, 1989 (Box 821, Folder 2)
      - Georgia, Atlanta, November 20, 1990 (Box 821, Folder 3)
      - Georgia, Savannah, March 25, 1991 (Box 821, Folder 4)
      - Hawaii, Honolulu, August 8, 1989 (Box 821, Folder 5)
      - Illinois, Chicago, June 27, 1989 (Box 821, Folder 6)
      - Illinois, Chicago, August 2, 1989 (Box 821, Folder 7)
      - Illinois, Chicago, August 20, 1990 (Box 821, Folder 8)
      - Illinois, Chicago, April 29, 1991 (Box 821, Folder 9)
      - Illinois, Chicago, February 7, 1990 (Box 821, Folder 10)
      - Iowa, Des Moines and Cedar Rapids, February 8, 1990 (Box 821, Folder 11)
      - Iowa, Des Moines, March 9, 1991 (Box 821, Folder 12)
      - Kansas, Wichita, June 6, 1991 (Box 821, Folder 13)
      - Kentucky, Louisville, October 2, 1990 (Box 821, Folder 14)
      - Louisiana, New Orleans, May 8, 1989 (Box 821, Folder 15)
      - Louisiana, New Orleans, November 30, 1990 (Box 821, Folder 16)
      - Louisiana, New Orleans, January 8, 1991 (Box 821, Folder 17)
      - Maine, Portland, July 18, 1989 (Box 821, Folder 18)
      - Maryland, Baltimore, November 16, 1990 (Box 821, Folder 19)
      - Massachusetts, Boston, December 10, 1988 (Box 821, Folder 20)
      - Massachusetts, Boston, March 26, 1990 (Box 821, Folder 21)
      - Massachusetts, Boston, July 27, 1990 (Box 821, Folder 22)
      - Massachusetts, Boston, September 14, 1990 (Box 821, Folder 23)
      - Massachusetts, Boston, May 17, 1991 (Box 821, Folder 24)
      - Massachusetts, Hyannis Port, August 18, 1990 (Box 821, Folder 25)
      - Michigan, Grand Rapids, October 17, 1990 (Box 821, Folder 26)
      - Minnesota, Minneapolis, June 26, 1990 (Box 821, Folder 27)
      - Missouri, Kansas City, January 23, 1990 (Box 821, Folder 28)
      - Missouri, Kansas City, July 20, 1990 (Box 821, Folder 29)
      - Missouri, Kansas City, October 25, 1990 (Box 821, Folder 30)
      - Missouri, Kansas City, August 7, 1991 (Box 821, Folder 31)
      - Missouri, Lake of the Ozarks, May 30, 1990 (Box 821, Folder 32)
      - Mississippi, Jackson (cancelled), undated (Box 821, Folder 33)
      - Nevada, Reno, November 9, 1990 (Box 821, Folder 34)
      - Nevada, Reno and Las Vegas, January 17, 1991 (Box 821, Folder 35)
      - New Hampshire, New Found Lake, July 18, 1989 (Box 821, Folder 36)
      - New Jersey, Stone Harbor, December 27, 1990 (Box 821, Folder 37)
      - New Jersey, Trenton, August 7, 1991 (Box 822, Folder 1)
      - New Mexico, Albuquerque and Santa Fe, May 2, 1990 (Box 822, Folder 2)
      - New York, New York City, May 25, 1989, June 19, 1989, May 4, 1989, November 23, 1988 (Box 822, Folder 3)
      - New York, New York City, October 26, 1989 (Box 822, Folder 4)
      - New York, New York City, January 6, 1990 (Box 822, Folder 5)
      - New York, New York City, July 13, 1990 (Box 822, Folder 6)
      - New York, New York City, November 2, 1990 (Box 822, Folder 7)
      - New York, New York City, March 2, 1991 (Box 822, Folder 8)
      - New York, New York City, May 11, 1991 (Box 822, Folder 9)
      - New York, New York City, February 7, 1990 (Box 822, Folder 10)
      - North Carolina, Chapel Hill, May 14, 1989 (Box 822, Folder 11)
      - Ohio, Canton, Cleveland and Columbus, May 11, 1989 (Box 822, Folder 12)
      - Ohio, Cincinnati, November 18, 1989 (Box 822, Folder 13)
      - Oklahoma, Tulsa, October 25, 1990 (Box 822, Folder 14)
      - Oregon, Portland, October 16, 1988 (Box 822, Folder 15)
      - Pennsylvania, Harrisburg, May 27, 1989 (Box 822, Folder 16)
      - Pennsylvania, Philadelphia, November 1, 1989, April 4, 1990, September 24, 1990 (Box 822, Folder 17)
      - Pennsylvania, Philadelphia, November 11, 1988, May 6, 1989 (Box 822, Folder 18)
      - Pennsylvania, Philadelphia, May 1, 1991 (Box 822, Folder 19)
      - Pennsylvania, Pittsburgh, November 14, 1988, April 3, 1990, April 11, 1989, September 12, 1989, May 16, 1989 (Box 822, Folder 20)
      - Pennsylvania, Pittsburgh, February 19, 1991 (Box 822, Folder 21)
      - Pennsylvania, Pittsburgh, August 14, 1991 (Box 822, Folder 22)
      - South Carolina, Charleston, October 7, 1988 (Box 822, Folder 23)
      - South Carolina, Columbia, April 30, 1990 (Box 822, Folder 24)
      - South Carolina, Hilton Head, November 13, 1989 (Box 822, Folder 25)
      - Tennessee, Nashville, Knoxville and Memphis, March 10, 1990 (Box 822, Folder 26)
      - Texas, Dallas and Fort Worth, June 13, 1989 (Box 823, Folder 1)
      - Texas, Dallas, October 31, 1990 (Box 823, Folder 2)
      - Texas, Dallas, May 22, 1991 (Box 823, Folder 3)
      - Texas, Houston, June 13, 1989 (Box 823, Folder 4)
      - Texas, San Antonio, September 26, 1989, April 20, 1989 (Box 823, Folder 5)
      - Texas, San Antonio, November 17, 1990 (Box 823, Folder 6)
      - Utah, Salt Lake City, May 31, 1990 (Box 823, Folder 7)
      - Virginia, Charlottesville, September 27, 1989 (Box 823, Folder 8)
      - Virginia, Richmond, April 16, 1990 (Box 823, Folder 9)
      - Virginia, Williamsburg, June 6, 1989 (Box 823, Folder 10)
      - Washington, Seattle, January 17, 1991 (Box 823, Folder 11)
      - Washington, Seattle and Spokane, March 21, 1990 (Box 823, Folder 12)
      - West Virginia, Charleston, February 3, 1989 (Box 823, Folder 13)
      - Wisconsin, Milwaukee, August 17, 1990 (Box 823, Folder 14)
  - Foreign Trips, 8.